https://www.equineadvocates.org/privacy-statement

Skip to content
HOMEABOUT USAbout Equine AdvocatesOur MissionWho We AreEmployment OpportunitiesPhoto GalleryAround the SanctuaryEquines & MoreFor the Love of HorsesHappenings & EventsIn Loving MemoryInstagramVideo GalleryTestimonialsSANCTUARYThe SanctuaryMeet Our ResidentsEducation CenterMain Barn2 or 3 Stall BarnFeed RoomPaddock GraphicsPond & Picnic AreaTHE ISSUESThe IssuesEquine RescueHorse SlaughterWhat You Can DoEquine Abuse & NeglectHow to Report Equine CrueltyWild Mustangs & BurrosWhat You Can DoPMU IndustryWhat You Can DoCarriage HorsesWhat You Can DoRodeo & Horse SoringWhat You Can DoCamp Horses/ Horses for HireWhat You Can DoResources & LinksHUMANE EDUCATIONKids CornerSUPPORTWays You Can HelpSingle DonationMonthly DonationSponsor an EquineOur Wish ListPlanned GivingDedicate a StallDedicate a BenchDedicate a TreeDedicate a 2 or 3-Stall BarnVolunteerChildren’s BookNote CardsWinter Note Cards2021 Anniversary CalendarMaskNEWS & UPDATESEA News & UpdatesSignup for eAlerts or Mailing ListCONTACTContact Equine AdvocatesSignup for eAlerts or Mailing ListMY ACCOUNT
Search for:
Equine Advocates Privacy Statement
By accessing Equine Advocates’ website (the “Site”) you are assenting to the terms of this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use. This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for the Site and applies solely to information collected by Equine Advocates through contacts initiated through the Site. It notifies you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to prevent the misuse of your information.
Information collection, use, and sharing
Equine Advocates is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only collect / have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We do not sell, share, or rent personal information collected from our visitors to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement.
Our website hosting company collects information to provide statistics on visits to the Site. Visitor information is compiled in aggregate and does not represent individually identifiable information.
We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you more about Equine Advocates.
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us by phone at (518) 245-1599 or through the Site.
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information, your information is protected, online and offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Personal information is stored in password-controlled computers with limited access.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us.
By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of personal information as described above. If we decide to change our Privacy Statement, we will post these changes so our visitors are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. We encourage you to check this page from time to time because your continued use of the Site following any changes to the Privacy Statement will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such changes.
ABOUT US
Who We Are
Employment Opportunities
Photo Gallery
Around the Sanctuary
Equines & More
For the Love of Horses
Happenings & Events
Donate Today!
From: $5.00
Your gift supports our equine residents.
*Make a One-Time donation below, or click to make a Monthly Donation
Donation Amount
Choose an option$25$50$75$100$250Other Amount
Clear selection
DONATE NOW
